Hello hello friends welcome to my channel you
unlock how are you guys I hope you guys are like this
so today I am going to share a very good trick with you guys it is a
very
good product because every product
is a waste product and its brand is beneficial by
pranking
all the products are herbal
and are very good products, it does
not have any side effects so today
I will share with you what is the
product so this is a pen product the first
product is our rose water which is
very important for our face
and the second is face serum and the third lip balm
Bhole Baba is very important for our lips
and especially in the winter season it is
very much and the winter season is about to come so
then we look at the packing one by one we
box it and we use it once to
see what is there and
what is not there and we will share its experience
with our loved ones so this is rose
water and we also use rose water everyday
and it is very important for our face
And
when in the olden times people used rose water a lot,
they used to
mix rose water in clay and apply it on their face,
you used to apply it there, rose water is of good use there
and all the ayurvedic
creams also contain rose water
and everyone should use rose water, it does
not harm our face at all,
so now we open it, it is
packed well in the box,
its box is also very beautiful,
drink it very quickly and now we take it out
and this is
water and see it is beautiful in a way,
plus egg
subscription, the product which is very good,
if it is not like the other, then
our
product based on that also goes,
that product
goes and after that, it is in
this way, it has a
very good smell and the
product which is there is also very
good and it will be
called very good, that is good, when we touch it, it feels
very good and now let us
see the second product
which is this face serum and I am seeing
how good it is by combining the pack  It is given
and now we open it,
so now we take it out in this way
and this serum bottle is such a
beautiful little bottle and how to use it,
so we have to use it,
wash the paste from it and after that you
spread the rose water and
after doing this, we have to massage two or three drops of
it on your face thoroughly
and after that you
can apply stitches here or sunscreen and this is that
product which is very small and very
cute and this is lip balm and now we
open it, see
[music] I want it
in such a beautiful pot and
this is of course a
and look at this
and the suggestion is
coming out of it in a very good time, so you have to
use it, it is
not a big deal, you just have to take face wash and
mix it well and apply it normally
now I have to write it and I will
also tell you the prices of all these, so first of all the
price of rose water is
29 and its  After this, there is
this serum, its price is 499 and the third one
which is our Libas, its price is 29
and if you people like any product
and
if you people want this product then I will put it in the description, from
there you
can click on all the products and the Khadi product,
you can change it from its best side
or you can change it with any app
and if you people liked my
video then I
would like to like the video, if you are a family then subscribe to the channel
and do
not forget to share the video at all and if you
can give suggestions to people or want to tell something
or want to open something then you
can tell by commenting, so I am leaving, I will see you
in the next video, till then
bye-bye